https://www.prasadgifts.com/index.php/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Cookie Policy
Our website uses cookies. By using our website, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with our Cookies Policy.
WHOLESALE LOG IN
We are sorry for the inconvenience but international orders need to be placed by calling 641-472-4334.
Prasad Gifts
BRINGING BEAUTY AND JOY TO LIFE
CLIMATE JUSTICE NOW!
FOR RETAIL
CUSTOMERS:
Search:
Our Commitment to Privacy
We are very grateful that you have chosen to shop at PrasadGifts.com. Part of our high standards of service is our committed to protecting your privacy online. Below, we explain how we collect, use and protect the information you provide to us. We sincerely respect your privacy and will try to give you as much control as possible over your personal information as possible.
The Information We Collect
Information You Provide Us
We accept and store any information that you submit on PrasadGifts.com or by telephone and email. For example, you may provide personal information when placing an order, enter a contest, request a catalog, or call or email us. This information may include your name, address, phone numbers, email address, credit card and payment information, and other personal information.
Telephone Calls with Prasad Gifts, Inc.
Prasad Gifts, Inc. does not record either outbound or inbound calls.
Web Site Use Information
We collect and analyze technical information about how customers interact with PrasadGifts.com including, but not limited to, IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, pages viewed, links, dates and times, and other information.
Cookies
Like many websites, we utilize a standard technology called "cookies" to differentiate you from other shoppers and to store and retrieve information about your interaction with our website, like the items in your shopping cart, for example.
Email Information and Contact Forms
We may collect, store, and use any information that you submit via email or any of the forms on our website. We may also collect information about email communications such as confirming that an email was opened or which links were clicked.
How We May Use Collected Information
We may use collected information for the purpose of administering our business activities such as completing and tracking orders, customer service, communicating with customers, administering giveaways and other promotions, customizing the shopping experience, troubleshooting, improving the website design and functionality, and other business uses. From time to time, we may send you promotional messages by mail or email. You will always have the option to opt out of such communications (see below).
As required by law, we do not intentionally share your information with third parties except to facilitate business operations (such as shipping partners and payment processors).
What We Do To Protect Your Information
In order to protect your information, we have put in place appropriate electronic, physical, and procedural safeguards. We utilize standard encryption/security technology to protect data transfer and our information systems are treated with the highest regard for security. In addition, we limit access to customer information to only authorized personnel.
How You Can Review or Correct Your Information
To review or correct your personal information, or to change your communication preferences, please call us at (800) 772-7231. Our customer service personnel will be glad to help. You may choose to stop receiving promotional communications at any time. If you have subscribed to any of our email newsletters, you may unsubscribe anytime.
Links to Other Websites
Prasad Gifts, Inc. is not responsible for the content or practices employed by other websites that are linked to from PrasadGifts.com. When you use a link to go from PrasadGifts.com to another website, our privacy policy is no longer in effect.
Your Consent
By using our website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
This policy was last updated on June 21, 2018. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please call us at (800) 772-7231 or contact us.
Prasad Premium Incense
Sai Baba Nag Champa
Native Smudge Sticks
Tibetan Herbal Incense
Mothers Incense
Shanthimalai Incense
Spanish Series Incense
Sai Flora Incense
You have no items to compare.
Have Questions or Comments?
Email Us
Call Us: 1-800-772-7231 (USA Only)
1-641-472-4334 (Local and International)
Write Us:Prasad Gifts, Inc.502 South 4th StreetFairfield, IA 52556, U.S.A.1-800-772-7231
HELPFUL ARTICLES
Burning Incense
FREE NEWSLETTER
Get Our Free Newsletter for SalesCoupon Codes, Specials and new Product announcements.
Find Us On:
visamasterpaypalmoney bookers
close
Continue Shopping
View cart & checkout
